# **OMORUYI KINGSLEY**

7, Ehidiamen Street, Ekpoma, Edo State

Mobile: 08164334818 E-mail: omoruyikingsley7@gmail.com

## PERSONAL PROFILE STATEMENT

A motivated, adaptable and responsible IT professional seeking a position in an IT position which will utilise the professional and technical skills developed through past work experiences in this field. I have a methodical, customer-focused approach to work and a strong drive to see things through to completion. In my current job, I have trained over 50 final year Computer Students undergoing Industrial Training over the past 2 years.

#### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

• Trained over 50 industrial trainees from Ambrose Alli University in the last 2 years.

### **EDUCATION**

#### 2000 – 2006

### **Ravic Education Centre**

8 O'Level Credit Passes

### 2006 - Present

 Taken several professional online courses on Web Development, Digital Marketing, Business Management, Leadership, and Self Improvement.

### **EMPLOYMENT**

# Nov 2016 – Present Senior IT Instructor, Euphoric Multitech Ltd.

- Oversee other IT instructors.
- Prepare training materials for instructors and students.
- Oversee operational activities.
- Train instructors and Industrial Trainees.

# Jan 2010 – Mar 2010 Café Attendant, Dercworld Cyber Café

- Administer browsing credit to clients.
- Perform regular system maintenance.

# **QUALIFICATIONS**

• Certificate of completion, Coding Fundamentals I & II

### **SKILLS**

- Excellent knowledge of a variety of programming languages including PHP, Javascript and Python.
- Strong troubleshooting skills with computer hardware.

### **HOBBIES AND INTERESTS**

I enjoy reading fiction books and researching wealth creation opportunities.

### **REFERENCES**

# Mrs. Evelyn Agbonze

Director

Kings Multipurpose Ltd.

**Address:** 1, Agbonze St., Ekenwan Barracks, Edo State

**Mobile:** 07033227271

### Mr. Leo Ekata Oni

Chief Executive Officer

**Euphoric Multitech Ltd** 

Address: 1, Ihumudumu Rd, Ekpoma, Edo State

**Mobile:** 08063587974